emailcenterpro.com 2016-11-30

# Privacy Statement - Email Center Pro

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for emailcenterpro.com, which is owned and operated by Palo Alto Software, Inc. If you have any questions or concerns about this statement, please contact us.

Palo Alto Software, Inc. collects personal information about our users only during the secure order process, the registration process for the free trial, or if you request other information sent to you. We collect name, email address, shipping address, credit card company, credit card number, expiration date, and credit card billing address. This is all kept strictly confidential.

To log into the service, we require that you accept a cookie. This is only for functionality reasons, and your personal information is never shared with anyone else.

We use a third-party tracking service called Google Analytics that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate such as usage and volume statistics in order to customize our interface for improved usability. These cookies help keep track of your login information to speed up the login process, and in certain cases we store your preferences to help tailor our site content to your interests. In the case that you choose not to accept cookies or if your browser automatically does not accept cookies, the only part of our site that will not work for you is the signup process.

Palo Alto Software, Inc. respects your right to privacy. We have a strict policy of not selling our customers' email addresses and are completely anti-spam. Our online store is fully secure and VeriSign has authenticated us as a secure site. We use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption for your credit card transactions, and we are authorized by VeriSign. We do share your credit card information with a third party only for verification purposes. All customer information available to internal employees is only accessible on our internal company network.

Palo Alto Software, Inc. uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties which receive the information. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, Palo Alto Software will cover your liability up to $50 provided that the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases.

Palo Alto Software will not disclose to any third party any information or data submitted by users of this website without the user's prior permission unless Palo Alto Software has a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; or (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Palo Alto Software.

The data we collect is used in the aggregate to give us demographic information about the entire Palo Alto Software, Inc. audience in order to improve our products and services. The information you provide -- name, address, etc. -- allows us to keep you informed about upgrades, products and services of Palo Alto Software, Inc., its affiliates and other third parties that we believe may be of interest to you. If you are a registered user of one of our products, we will only send information regarding your product or any assistance you require. We do not send our business planning newsletter automatically: you will only receive it if you specifically register for it. We only share aggregate information (i.e. number of users, referral URLs, etc.) -- not individual data -- with our advertisers to help them better understand our services and to monitor the reach of their advertising.

If you would like to modify, update or delete information that is collected through ordering, or registration please contact customerservice@paloalto.com or call 1-800-605-7057.

Legal Disclaimer: We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our website.

If you have questions, we can be reached by email at customerservice@paloalto.com or 1-800-605-7057.

Effective Date: 02/22/08

44 West Broadway, Suite 500  
Eugene, OR 97401, USA  
(800) 605-7057
